http://www.truckmasterlogistics.com/privacy-policy#PTop

Privacy Policy
TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc.
http://www.truckmaster.com
Effective from 25th of November 2008 to 25th of November 2009.
General Information
TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices.
This policy covers what personally identifiable information TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. collects and how it is treated.
Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www.truckmaster.com Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number.
This policy only applies to http://www.truckmaster.com and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.
Contact Information
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy.
Our Internet address is located at http://www.truckmaster.com
TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc.
506 South Adams
Jerome 83338
Idaho USA
You may contact us by e-mail at myprivacy@truckmaster.com
You may contact us by phone on (208) 324-5191
Dispute Resolution
TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently.
Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative.
Our customer service will promptly correct any errors.
TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. is P3PSeal certified. In the event that a dispute regarding our privacy practices cannot be settled through our normal dispute resolution processes,
you should contact P3PSeal, an independent third party. P3PSeal will serve as a liaison with TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. to resolve any dispute you may have.
Information Collection
When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected.
This section explains what information TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. collects, and how it is used.
Information Collected - What information do we collect and why?
We collect the following identifiable information about our visitors:
General area of Web Site
dynamic.clickstream
dynamic.http
dynamic.clientevents
dynamic.searchtext
dynamic.cookies
dynamic.miscdata
Conversion area of Web Site
dynamic.miscdata
We collect identifiable information for the following reasons:
General area of Web Site
Completion and Support of Current Activity
Web Site and System Administration
Research and Development
Pseudonymous Analysis
Pseudonymous Decision
Individual Analysis
Individual Decision
Individual Decision
Analytical data collected is used to provide our visitors with a better experience.
The data you provide to us is used to return your requests for information about our products.
Information Recipients - Who has access to the information collected?
General area of Web Site
Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent.
Conversion area of Web Site
Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent.
Information Retention - How long is this information retained?
General area of Web Site
We do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site.
Conversion area of Web Site
We do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site.
Opt-In / Opt-OutGeneral area of Web SiteIf you wish to either opt-in or opt-out of the use of the information collected in this area of our Web Site, you may do so by going to:
www.truckmaster.com/opt-out
Conversion area of Web SiteIf you wish to either opt-in or opt-out of the use of the information collected in this area of our Web Site, you may do so by going to:
www.truckmaster.com/opt-out
Cookies
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site.
A cookie is an element of data that a Web Site can send to your browser, which may then store it on
your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance
to decide whether to accept it.
Our Web site uses the following cookies:
name="vid" value="*" domain=".truckmaster.com" path="/"
name="vid" value="*" domain=".truckmaster.com" path="/"
Given highest ratings by industry experts. Highly recommended by our customers.
"I have used TruckMaster software and hardware for over 10 years. I am very pleased with not only the product but also the service I have needed and received!"—Michael D. Fenters,C&S Brokerage Product(s): Freight Broker Software
"We have been using TruckMaster since 1998.. We like the flow from the beginning to the end.. When customers or carriers call for information, in a very short time we can track it. Customer support is always available. We highly recommend this program."—Danny Hunsberger,Home Again Product(s): Freight Broker Software
"TruckMaster had the base product we were looking for. They were able to quickly integrate the new features we requested... We feel very strongly about our partnership with TruckMaster and would recommend them to anyone."—Robert H. Gibbs,Third Coast Exchange, Inc. Product(s): Logistics Software
Ask Us
About Our Fee-Based
Online ASP Product
Priced For Smaller Companies!
Fuel Finder (FREE)
RequestA FreeDemo!
ASK ABOUTOUR IN-HOUSEFINANCING
Ask For Your Free Online Demonstration Today To See What TruckMaster Can Do For Your Transportation Business!
| Copyright © 2011 TruckMaster Logistics Systems, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
